<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kpops on New X Theme</title>
    <link>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kpops on New X Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 21:00:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Award-winning My Gran&#39;s Lentil Soup</title>
      <link>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1010-step-by-step-guide-to-make-award-winning-my-gran-s-lentil-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 21:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1010-step-by-step-guide-to-make-award-winning-my-gran-s-lentil-soup/</guid>
      <description>My Gran&amp;#39;s Lentil SoupHey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, my gran&#39;s lentil soup. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
My Gran&#39;s Lentil Soup is one of the most popular of current trending foods on earth. It is easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick Tattie Soup</title>
      <link>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1012-recipe-of-quick-tattie-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 20:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1012-recipe-of-quick-tattie-soup/</guid>
      <description>Tattie SoupHello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, tattie soup. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Tattie Soup is one of the most well liked of current trending meals on earth. It is enjoyed by millions daily. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Summer Marrow Soup with Chilli, Lime, Mint and Garlic</title>
      <link>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1007-recipe-of-perfect-summer-marrow-soup-with-chilli-lime-mint-and-garlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 19:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1007-recipe-of-perfect-summer-marrow-soup-with-chilli-lime-mint-and-garlic/</guid>
      <description>Summer Marrow Soup with Chilli, Lime, Mint and GarlicHey everyone, it is Jim, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, summer marrow soup with chilli, lime, mint and garlic. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Summer Marrow Soup with Chilli, Lime, Mint and Garlic is one of the most popular of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Perfect Garlic soup</title>
      <link>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1009-simple-way-to-prepare-perfect-garlic-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 15:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1009-simple-way-to-prepare-perfect-garlic-soup/</guid>
      <description>Garlic soupHey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, garlic soup. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
This hearty garlic soup recipe takes all the health benefits of garlic to the next level. Roasted garlic adds savory sweetness along with flavorful (and healthful) chicken broth, onions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Bone Soup (Sup Tulang)</title>
      <link>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1006-recipe-of-perfect-bone-soup-sup-tulang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 11:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://derecipe-cuisine.netlify.app/kpop/1006-recipe-of-perfect-bone-soup-sup-tulang/</guid>
      <description>Bone Soup (Sup Tulang)Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, bone soup (sup tulang). One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Bone Soup (Sup Tulang) is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions every day. It is simple, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
